Soobin
You were in trouble
because of me today
No, it's nothing
You were not that bad
compared to others
Wait
Your lips are swollen
You worked too hard
on the kiss scene
I would've done better
if I worked that hard
Come on, it was your
first kiss scene ever
Hey, he was dead drunk
He can't even
remember anything
Don't talk bullshit
Well, I could've had
some fun while drunk
But Hyesung, that punk
is fucking naive…
Say that again
What did you do
to Hyesung?
Hey, calm down
I haven't done
anything yet
You crazy bastard!
Hey, why are you
being so dramatic?
I guess Hyesung
is dating another guy
Damn it
Touch Lee Hyesung
one more time
and I won't let it slide
God damn it!
I'm finished
Uh, you're here
You did a great job
How about we ask Yoo-il
to go to the wrap party…
Yoo-il?
He left earlier
Did he?
Yes
Hop on, let's go
to the party
Come on